Jose Chavarria Full Stack Developer

josechavarria@me.com | Cell. +39 3791553968 | Sardinia, Italy

Portfolio: https://pascu.dev

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/josechavarriafullstack/

Github: https://github.com/pascuch

Full Stack Developer with Frontend orientation. Having participated in individual and group projects, I was able to learn working methodologies in development teams. In these projects I used tools such as React, Redux, Node, Express, SQL, HTML, Sass, perfecting myself with Javascript. Passionate about technology and the solutions they provide to everyday life. I worked more than 10 years in accounting and supply areas, in this process I acquired new learning routes and ways to solve the problems that arise.

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, Sass, Javascript, React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Postgres, Sequelize, SCRUM.

PROJECTS

Frontend Developer – Netflix Clone

July 2022 - Present

Github: https://github.com/pascuch/netflix-clone

Deploy: https://netflix.pascu.dev

Personal project to master my stack of technologies and implement new ones. This project consists in cloning the Netflix application successively incorporating new functionalities.

Features:

- Login with mail and Facebook,
- Authentication and backend implemented with Firebase
- Main screen with recommended and movies grouped by genres
- API used: TMDB
- User screen
- Subscription plans
- Payment gateway with Stripe
- Log out
- Styles with Tailwind

Frontend Developer - Rental App

May 2022

Henry Bootcamp - Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Repo: https://github.com/nicolascohen24/rental-client

- Development of accommodation booking app. It was carried out in four weeks with a team of 8
 developers (divided into Frontend and Backend) following the SCRUM methodology, presenting
 progress to the Product Owner every week.
- Worked in Frontend team with technologies such as HTML, CSS, React, Redux, Sass, Javascript.
- Asigned and developed the different app components.

The application is characterized by including the following functionalities:

- o Accommodation search engine according to user preferences
- o Booking Manager

- o Payment gateway (implemented with Mercadopago)
- o Authentication with Passport
- o Google integration for login
- o Admin dashboard
- o System to create and manage acommodations

Full Stack Web Developer - Pokemon App

April 2022

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Deploy: https://pascuch-pokemon.vercel.app

Repo: https://github.com/pascuch/PI-Pokemon

- SPA development in which all the knowledge acquired in the FullStack Bootcamp was integrated. For this app, technologies such as React, Redux, pure HTML and CSS were used for the frontend and NodeJS, Express, Sequelize for the backend.
- In the development, an external API was used to integrate it with the own database in which new functionalities were added.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Purchasing Analyst

August 2019 - May 2022

Ledesma SA - Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Evaluating suppliers and managing relationships
- Negotiating contract terms of agreement and pricing,
- Preparing financial budget

Accounting Assistant

March 2012 – August 2019

Puerto Seco SA - Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Prepared balance sheet reports
- Prepared financial Budget
- Prepared tax returns

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Full Stack Web Developer Henry Bootcamp 2022
- Accountant Universidad Argentina de la Empresa (UADE) 2020
- Bachelor in Business Administration Universidad Argentina de la Empresa (UADE) 2018

LANGUAJES

- Ingles B2 Upper intermediate (TOEFL exam)
- Spanish Native

SKILLS

- Decision-making
- Teamwork
- Proactiv

- Creativity
- Problem-solving
- Adaptability